import { Question } from "@/types/Question";

export const questionsByWeek: { [week: string]: Question[] } = {
  week1: [
    {
      question: "What is the resin code of Low density polyethylene (LDPE)?",
      options: ["1", "3", "4", "6"],
      answer: "4",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following statement is correct?",
      options: ["Plastics can be both thermally and electrically conductive.", ". Plastics have very low strength to weight ratio.", "Plastics can be very resistant to chemicals and corrosion.", "Plastics are not water resistant. "],
      answer: "Plastics can be very resistant to chemicals and corrosion.",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is not a thermoplastic?",
      options: ["Teflon", "Polyurethane", "Nylon", "Polycarbonate"],
      answer: "Polyurethane",
    },
    {
      question:"Which country is the largest producer of plastic material?",
      options: ["India", "United States of America", "China", "Russia"],
      answer: "China",
    },
    {
      question: "According to Plastic Europe market research group (PEMRG), which is the market sector having largest plastic demand",
      options: ["Packaging", "Automotive", "Electrical & Electronics", "Agriculture"],
      answer: "Packaging",
    },
    {
      question: "Which country has the highest percapita plastic products consumption, according to FICCI report, 2017?",
      options: [
        "Brazil",
        "Indonesia",
        "China",
        "United States of America",
      ],
      answer: "United States of America",
    },
    {
      question: "Which type of plastic has highest demand in India, as per Chemicals & Petrochemical Statistics, 2013?",
      options: ["LLDPE", ". PET", "PVC", "HDPE"],
      answer: "PVC",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Stabilizers are type of additives added while producing plastics to:",
      options: ["remove fire-propagating radicals like H ,OH and others", "prolong the lifetime of the polymer by suppressing degradation", "improve the plasticity and to impart softness to the plastic", "impart strength, hardness and other properties to the plastic"],
      answer: "prolong the lifetime of the polymer by suppressing degradation",
    },
    {
      question: "Which type of plastic is called as “Poison Plastic”?",
      options: [
        "LDPE",
        "PS",
        "PET",
        "PVC",
      ],
      answer: "PVC",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is/are additives added to enhance the property of plastics?",
      options: [
        "Fillers",
        "Plasticizers",
        "lubricants ",
        "All of the above",
      ],
      answer: "All of the above",
    },
    {
      question: "HDPE is the most commonly recycled plastic because it will not break under exposure to extreme heat or cold",
      options: [
        "True",
        "False",
      ],
      answer: "True",
    },
    {
      question: "Thermosetting plastics can be recycled",
      options: [
        "True",
        "False",
      ],
      answer: "False",
    },
    {
      question: "Elastomers deform considerably under load at room temperature and return to their original shape, when the load is released",
      options: [
        "True",
        "False",
      ],
      answer: "True",
    },
    {
      question: "Chemical composition of thermoplastics changes on heating",
      options: [
        "True",
        "False",
      ],
      answer: "False",
    },
    {
      question: "Plastics are materials with a seemingly limitless range of characteristics and colors and are easy to manufacture",
      options: [
        "True",
        "False",
      ],
      answer: "True",
    },
  ],
  week2: [
    {
      question: "Which sector is the maximum contributor to plastic waste, according to Mudgal et al., (2011)?",
      options: ["Agriculture", "Building & Construction", "Packaging", "Automobile"],
      answer: "Packaging",
    },
    {
      question: "What are small pieces of plastic derived from the breakdown of larger plastic debris called?",
      options: ["Microbeads.", "Micro plastics", "Plastic pellets.", "Scrubbers"],
      answer: "Micro plastics",
    },
    {
      question: "Which river is the highest contributor of plastic waste?",
      options: ["Yangtze", "Indus", "Nile", "Amazon"],
      answer: "Yangtze",
    },
    {
      question:"Which is the lowest consumed virgin plastic resin in India according to world scientific publishing co. 2014?",
      options: ["LDPE", "HDPE", "PVC", "PS"],
      answer: "PS",
    },
    {
      question: "From 1970 to 1995, which component of the MSW has recorded the highest growth rate in weight proportion, according to world scientific publishing co. 2014?",
      options: ["Plastics", "Glass", " Paper", "Metals"],
      answer: "Plastics",
    },
    {
      question: "Which state is the largest producer of plastic waste in India according to CPCB report, 2017?",
      options: [
        "Tamilnadu",
        "Maharashtra",
        "Gujarat",
        "Punjab",
      ],
      answer: "Maharashtra",
    },
    {
      question: "According to Eunomia consultant firm of UK, what is the amount of plastic entering the marine environment?",
      options: ["9.8 Million tonnes per annum", ". 10.3 Million tonnes per annum", "11.5 Million tonnes per annum", "12.2 Million tonnes per annum"],
      answer: "12.2 Million tonnes per annum",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following statement(s) is/are correct?",
      options: ["Primary sources of plastic waste undergo fragmentation & degradation to form secondary sources.", "Plastics that act as pollutants can be categorized into micro-, meso-, or macro debris, based on size.", "Plastic waste can be of both aesthetic and environmental nuisance when on land", "All the above"],
      answer: "All the above",
    },
    {
      question: "According to ourworlddata.org, which type of plastic waste source (by plastic use) is of greatest mass in the Great pacific garbage patch?",
      options: [
        "Hard plastic, plastic sheet & film",
        "Plastic lines, ropes & fishing nets",
        "Preproduction plastic pellets",
        "Foamed plastic material",
      ],
      answer: "Plastic lines, ropes & fishing nets",
    },
    {
      question: "According to Ericksen et al., 2014, which ocean/marine basin has the largest quantity of plastic waste floating at the ocean surface?",
      options: [
        "North Pacific",
        "North Atlantic",
        "South Pacific ",
        "South Atlantic",
      ],
      answer: "North Pacific",
    },
    {
      question: "Marine litter is human-created waste that has been deliberately or accidentally released into a sea or ocean during shipping, fishing or aquacultures.",
      options: [
        "True",
        "False",
      ],
      answer: "True",
    },
    {
      question: "Micro beads are not used in various personal care and cosmetic products. ",
      options: [
        "True",
        "False",
      ],
      answer: "False",
    },
    {
      question: "Plastic litter directly into the rivers, streams and drains can be a cause of clogging of drains and can be breading spaces for mosquitos causing human health hazard",
      options: [
        "True",
        "False",
      ],
      answer: "True",
    },
    {
      question: "Micro bead particles can easily be filtered out by wastewater plants?",
      options: [
        "True",
        "False",
      ],
      answer: "False",
    },
    {
      question: "Plastic Consumption in India by industrial goods sector is the highest according to, World Scientific Publishing Co, 2014",
      options: [
        "True",
        "False",
      ],
      answer: "False",
      },
  ],
  week3: [
    {
      "question": "Minimum thickness of plastic carry bags allowed, according to Plastic waste management rules (2016)?",
      "options": ["30 microns", "40 microns", "50 microns", "60 microns"],
      "answer": "50 microns"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is extended producer’s responsibility (EPR)?",
      "options": [
        "Responsibility of a producer for the economic sustainability of the product.",
        "Responsibility of a producer for working towards customer satisfaction of the product.",
        "Responsibility of a producer for the marketing of the product.",
        "Responsibility of a producer for the environmentally sound management of the product."
      ],
      "answer": "Responsibility of a producer for the environmentally sound management of the product."
    },
    {
      "question": "‘Ensuring that open burning of plastic waste does not take place’ is the responsibility of?",
      "options": [
        "Local bodies",
        "Gram Panchayats",
        "Producers",
        "Both (a) & (b)"
      ],
      "answer": "Both (a) & (b)"
    },
    {
      "question": "Producers, Importers & Brand Owners should ensure that the manufacturing and use of non-recyclable multi-layered plastic need to be phased out in how many years?",
      "options": ["5", "2", "3", "1"],
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the prescribed authority for enforcement of provisions for registration, manufacturing of plastic products, processing & disposal of plastic waste in states?",
      "options": [
        "Pollution control boards",
        "Pollution control committees",
        "Secretary in-charge of urban development",
        "Gram panchayats"
      ],
      "answer": "Pollution control boards"
    },
    {
      "question": "One of the targets of Sustainable development goal 14 (SDG 14) in the United Nations 2030 Agenda for Sustainable Development is?",
      "options": [
        "To ensure availability and sustainable management of water and sanitation for all.",
        "To build resilient infrastructure, promote inclusive and sustainable industrialization, and foster innovation",
        "To prevent and significantly reduce marine pollution of all kinds, in particular from land-based activities, including marine debris and nutrient pollution.",
        "To end hunger, achieve food security and improved nutrition, and promote sustainable agriculture"
      ],
      "answer": "To prevent and significantly reduce marine pollution of all kinds, in particular from land-based activities, including marine debris and nutrient pollution."
    },
    {
      "question": "Which countries among the Group of seven have not signed the charter with one of its aim is to increase plastic recycling?",
      "options": [
        "United Kingdom and China",
        "Japan and United states",
        "France and United Kingdom",
        "Canada and United States"
      ],
      "answer": "Japan and United states"
    },
    {
      "question": "According to the 25 year environmental plan outlined by UK in 2018, achievement of zero avoidable plastic waste is to be achieved by the end of which year?",
      "options": ["2042", "2035", "2050", "2038"],
      "answer": "2042"
    },
    {
      "question": "If you want to establish a plastic carry bags manufacturing factory in Kolkata, from where do you have to obtain registration?",
      "options": [
        "Pollution control committee (PCC)",
        "State pollution control board (SPCB)",
        "Chief secretary of the state",
        "Gram panchayat"
      ],
      "answer": "State pollution control board (SPCB)"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am running a plastic recycling plant and I have to renew my validity of my registration certificate before it is going to expire. Before how many days should I apply for renewal?",
      "options": ["120 days", "90 days", "150 days", "30 days"],
      "answer": "120 days"
    },
    {
      "question": "Plastic Waste management rules (2016) are applicable to waste generators only.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "All institutional waste generators shall segregate and store the waste in accordance with municipal solid waste management rules (2016).",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "Any person can manufacture carry bags or recycle plastic bags without obtaining any registration from SPCB or PCC.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "According to PWM rules (2016), carry bags made of recycled plastic can be used for storing or packaging ready to eat or drink food stuff.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "The process of transforming segregated plastic waste into a new product or raw material for producing new products is called recycling.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "True"
    },
  ],
  week4: [
    {
      "question": "Which was the first state in India to achieve the plastic bag-free status?",
      "options": ["Maharashtra", "Sikkim", "Goa", "Gujarat"],
      "answer": "Sikkim"
    },
    {
      "question": "As part of its 25 year plan to eliminate plastic waste, which country has banned the use of plastic microbeads in cosmetic & personal care products?",
      "options": ["United States", "Netherlands", "Germany", "United Kingdom"],
      "answer": "United Kingdom"
    },
    {
      "question": "‘As of National Sword policy enacted by China in 2017, what is the maximum contamination limit set for importing recycled materials?",
      "options": ["0.5%", "0.3%", "0.4%", "0.2%"],
      "answer": "0.5%"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which policy was implemented by Chinese government aimed at curtailing the amount of contaminated recyclables and waste in 2013?",
      "options": ["BLUE SKY", "RED LIGHT", "DRAGON FIRE", "GREEN FENCE"],
      "answer": "GREEN FENCE"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the major implication(s) of National sword policy of China?",
      "options": [
        "Increased investment in countries where waste material originates",
        "New recycling facilities in other Asian countries",
        "Increased demand for feasible alternatives",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which country is the largest cumulative exporter of plastic waste to China from 1986 to 2016 as per UN Comtrade (International Trade Statistics Database)?",
      "options": ["United States", "Japan", "Hong Kong", "Germany"],
      "answer": "Hong Kong"
    },
    {
      "question": "In 2018, Indian government has announced the ban of single use of plastic items by which year?",
      "options": ["2025", "2022", "2024", "2030"],
      "answer": "2022"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the waste imports inspections program launched by the Chinese customs authorities in 2018 to succeed/replace the National sword policy, 2017?",
      "options": ["BLUE SKY", "RED LIGHT", "DRAGON FIRE", "GREEN FENCE"],
      "answer": "BLUE SKY"
    },
    {
      "question": "In response to China’s National sword policy 2017, the exports of scrap plastics from US to China dropped from 2017 to 2018 by what percentage (approx.)?",
      "options": ["32%", "7%", "92%", "53%"],
      "answer": "92%"
    },
    {
      "question": "As per UN Comtrade, which country is the largest cumulative importer of Polyethylene (PE) waste from 1986 to 2016 by net weight?",
      "options": ["Belgium", "Hong Kong", "China", "Malaysia"],
      "answer": "China"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bangladesh is the first country in the world to implement a ban on thin plastic bags.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "New recycling facilities in Asian countries were marked to increase due to national sword policy of china.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "Maharashtra was first state in India to achieve the plastic bag-free status.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "China filed notification to WTO that they intend to ban 24 categories of solid waste in the year 2014.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "The Reduction in China’s recycling volumes will strengthen virgin resin demand and prices",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "True"
    },
  ],
  week5: [
    {
      "question": "Which of the following toxic compound/s from plastic pollution has/have the property of mimicking estrogen?",
      "options": ["Styrene", "Bisphenol A", "Nonyl phenol", "Both (b) & (c)"],
      "answer": "Both (b) & (c)"
    },
    {
      "question": "Through which of the following process(es) plastic waste has an effect on the marine life?",
      "options": ["Ingestion", "Entanglement", "Bio magnification", "All the above"],
      "answer": "All the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which forms the largest source of ocean micro plastics worldwide as per city research, World Atlas 2018?",
      "options": ["Synthetic textiles", "Car tyres", "City dust", "Marine coatings"],
      "answer": "Synthetic textiles"
    },
    {
      "question": "Consumption of waste plastic mistakenly as food by fish and other wildlife which leads to their death is termed as?",
      "options": ["Entanglement", "Digestion", "Ingestion", "None of the above"],
      "answer": "Ingestion"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the largest of the five offshore plastic accumulation zones in the world's oceans?",
      "options": ["Indian Ocean Gyre", "North Atlantic gyre", "Arctic gyre", "Great pacific garbage patch"],
      "answer": "Great pacific garbage patch"
    },
    {
      "question": "The reason(s) for plastic ingestion by wild life is/are?",
      "options": [
        "Plastic microbeads resemble fish eggs and are often eaten by jellyfish, egg-eating fish and filter feeders",
        "Seabirds that skim the ocean surface while flying, such as albatrosses, cannot differentiate floating food from litter.",
        "Sonar of some animals can confuse plastic for squid and jellyfish.",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "Increase in concentrations of contaminants through transfer within a food web can be termed as?",
      "options": ["Eutrophication", "Bio magnification", "Bio stimulation", "Bio remediation"],
      "answer": "Bio magnification"
    },
    {
      "question": "Styrene monomers are found in which types of plastic?",
      "options": ["LDPE", "HDPE", "PS", "PVC"],
      "answer": "LDPE"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the reason(s) for which fishing gear can become marine litter?",
      "options": ["Fishing gear is abandoned", "Fishing gear is discarded", "Fishing gear is lost", "All of the above"],
      "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "Plastic pollution promotes mosquito breeding",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "Fishing Vessels are also a source of marine pollution.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "According to WWF report 2018, more than 1% of total plastic floats on the surface.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "Entanglement of discarded plastics can cause death of marine animals by drowning, suffocation, strangulation, or starvation.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dioxins are carcinogenic and a hormone disruptor and persistent, and they accumulate in our body-fat and thus mothers give it directly to their babies via the placenta.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "PTHALATES are commonly cited plastic additives.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "True"
    },
  ],
  week6: [
    {
      "question": "Which of the following process(es) is/are a part of mechanical recycling of plastics?",
      "options": ["Segregation", "Pelletization", "Extrusion", "All the above"],
      "answer": "All the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "During which process(es) does the plastic undergo molecular and structural level changes to produce products with unique properties than the raw materials?",
      "options": ["Incineration", "Mechanical Recycling", "Feedstock Recycling", "All of the above"],
      "answer": "Feedstock Recycling"
    },
    {
      "question": "The solid phase product produced during pyrolysis of plastics is called as?",
      "options": ["Synsolid", "Char", "Biocoal", "Ash"],
      "answer": "Char"
    },
    {
      "question": "The thermal degradation of plastic waste with continuous supply of oxygen is called as?",
      "options": ["Pyrolysis", "Gasification", "Incineration", "Mechanical Recycling"],
      "answer": "Incineration"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a feed point for the plastic waste materials into the cement production process in a cement kiln?",
      "options": ["The main burner at the rotary kiln outlet end", "The rotary kiln inlet end", "The pre-calciner", "Clinker"],
      "answer": "Clinker"
    },
    {
      "question": "Liquefied waste plastic is coated on which of this raw material of a road in the construction of a plastic road?",
      "options": ["Sand", "Bitumen", "Aggregate", "Cement"],
      "answer": "Aggregate"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following tertiary treatment processes is the most efficient micro plastics treatment mechanism in waste water treatment plant?",
      "options": ["Membrane bioreactor", "Disc filter", "Rapid sand filter", "Dissolved air floatation"],
      "answer": "Membrane bioreactor"
    },
    {
      "question": "Incineration of polystyrene produces which of the following toxic gases?",
      "options": ["Ethylene", "Methane", "Styrene", "All of the above"],
      "answer": "Styrene"
    },
    {
      "question": "The basic process of laying a plastic road follows which of these sequences?",
      "options": ["Segregation > Shredding> Cleaning", "Cleaning> Shredding> Segregation", "Shredding >Segregation > Cleaning", "Segregation > Cleaning> Shredding"],
      "answer": "Segregation > Cleaning> Shredding"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following plastic waste management option is endothermic in nature?",
      "options": ["Pyrolysis", "Mechanical recycling", "Incineration", "Landfilling"],
      "answer": "Pyrolysis"
    },
    {
      "question": "Pyrolysis of plastic waste involves breaking down of the plastics into products of only two phases: liquid and gas.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "By the process of incineration, high calorific value of the plastic waste produces very low amount of energy.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "Landfilling is a cheapest and easiest plastic waste management option.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "Plastic is not a very good binder.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "After the road laying, it is opined that the first rain will trigger leaching due to the mechanical abrasion of plastic which forms as a sticky layer.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": "True"
    },
  ],
  week7: [
    {
      "question": "Bioplastics are an assimilation of which of these characteristics?",
      "options": [
          "Bio based material & Water solubility",
          "Bio based material & Biodegradability",
          "Water solubility & Biodegradability",
          "Bio based material, Biodegradability & Water solubility"
      ],
      "answer": "Bio based material & Biodegradability"
  },
  {
      "question": "A bio based product can be defined as?",
      "options": [
          "The product is biodegradable",
          "The product degrades to form a biomass",
          "The raw material is at least partly derived from biomass (plants)",
          "All of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "The raw material is at least partly derived from biomass (plants)"
  },
  {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a disadvantage of bioplastics?",
      "options": [
          "Bioplastics do nothing to change consumer behaviour regarding their use of plastic products.",
          "They can interfere with or damage standard plastic recycling processes.",
          "They have a higher manufacturing cost.",
          "They reduce the use of fossil-fuels and reliance on non-renewable resources."
      ],
      "answer": "They reduce the use of fossil-fuels and reliance on non-renewable resources."
  },
  {
      "question": "Which of the following plastic of biodegradable polyester family is naturally produced renewable?",
      "options": [
          "AAC",
          "PHB",
          "PBAT",
          "PBSA"
      ],
      "answer": "PHB"
  },
  {
      "question": "Which types of synthetic polymers are incorporated with light-sensitive chemical additives to enhance its biodegradability in specific environments?",
      "options": [
          "Oxy-degradable plastics",
          "Starch based plastic",
          "Water soluble polymers",
          "Photo-biodegradable plastics"
      ],
      "answer": "Photo-biodegradable plastics"
  },
  {
      "question": "The plastic additives which promote oxidation processes that break the plastic down into brittle, low-molecular-weight fragments are?",
      "options": [
          "Prodegradant concentrates",
          "Ferrocene concentrates",
          "Diketone concentrates",
          "Carbonyl concentrates"
      ],
      "answer": "Prodegradant concentrates"
  },
  {
      "question": "The vegetative root that is used as an ingredient of a mushroom-based plastic replacement material is?",
      "options": [
          "Paraben",
          "Lignin",
          "Mycelium",
          "Casein"
      ],
      "answer": "Mycelium"
  },
  {
      "question": "The edible membrane that is used to encircle the drinking water developed by ‘Skipping Rock Labs’ is made from which raw material?",
      "options": [
          "Bagasse",
          "Sea weed",
          "Palm leaves",
          "Corn Starch"
      ],
      "answer": "Sea weed"
  },
  {
      "question": "Which of the following is a water-soluble synthetic plastic that is used as an oxygen barrier layer in multilayer film packaging?",
      "options": [
          "Polyhydroxylalkonates (PHA)",
          "Polyvinyl Alcohol (PVOH)",
          "Poly lactic acid (PLA)",
          "Ethylene Vinyl Alcohol (EVOH)"
      ],
      "answer": "Ethylene Vinyl Alcohol (EVOH)"
  },
  {
      "question": "An antimicrobial, antibacterial, and biodegradable carry bag produced by Everitt, a group of researchers from Nottingham and Nile University, uses which of the following as a raw material?",
      "options": [
          "Banana fiber",
          "Pineapple",
          "Shrimp shells",
          "Mushrooms"
      ],
      "answer": "Shrimp shells"
  },
  {
      "question": "Biodegradable plastics are not always compostable.",
      "options": [
          "True",
          "False"
      ],
      "answer": "True"
  },
  {
      "question": "Biodegradable plastic generally refers to a plastic that cannot be broken down by microorganisms in the environment within a fixed period of time.",
      "options": [
          "True",
          "False"
      ],
      "answer": "False"
  },
  {
      "question": "Polyvinyl Alcohol (PVOH) is a water-insoluble polymer.",
      "options": [
          "True",
          "False"
      ],
      "answer": "False"
  },
  {
      "question": "Bagasse products have good thermal properties which can sustain temperatures from -25°C to 220°C.",
      "options": [
          "True",
          "False"
      ],
      "answer": "True"
  },
  {
      "question": "Higher biodegradability of paper over film contributes to the environment-friendliness of a metallized paper.",
      "options": [
          "True",
          "False"
      ],
      "answer": "True"
    }
,
  ],
  week8: [
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements is false?",
      "options": [
          "In a circular economy, materials constantly flow around a ‘closed loop’ system",
          "Circular economy means keeping the value of products in the economy, without leakage into the natural environment",
          "In circular economy, the value of the material is lost, because they are discarded after being used once.",
          "Circular Economy is restorative and regenerative by design"
      ],
      "answer": "In circular economy, the value of the material is lost, because they are discarded after being used once."
  },
  {
      "question": "Which of the following is not an objective of circular economy?",
      "options": [
          "Transition to renewable energy sources",
          "Building economic, natural and social capital",
          "Creating demand for virgin raw materials from consumption of finite resources",
          "Redefining growth and focus on positive society-wide benefits"
      ],
      "answer": "Creating demand for virgin raw materials from consumption of finite resources"
  },
  {
      "question": "Which of the following areas is Unilever working on, to achieve its goal of moving towards a circular economy?",
      "options": [
          "Rethinking how to design their products",
          "Working with suppliers",
          "Following a linear approach of take, make & dispose",
          "Exploring solutions to price fluctuations in the material market"
      ],
      "answer": "Rethinking how to design their products"
  },
  {
      "question": "In 2017, Unilever committed to ensuring that 100% of their plastic packaging will be designed to be fully reusable, recyclable, or compostable. This target is to be achieved by which year?",
      "options": [
          "2020",
          "2025",
          "2030",
          "2035"
      ],
      "answer": "2025"
  },
  {
      "question": "Which of the following is a consortium of approximately 60 European companies, organizations, and associations across the entire value chain of flexible packaging?",
      "options": [
          "Plastics Europe",
          "European Plastics Distributors Association (EPDA)",
          "CEFLEX",
          "The Association of Plastics Manufacturers in Europe (APME)"
      ],
      "answer": "CEFLEX"
  },
  {
      "question": "Which of the following is a target(s) of the UK Plastic Pact for 2025?",
      "options": [
          "100% of plastic packaging to be reusable, recyclable or compostable",
          "70% of plastic packaging effectively recycled or composted",
          "30% average recycled content across all plastic packaging",
          "All of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
      "question": "The Packaging Recovery Notes (PRNs) are?",
      "options": [
          "Rewards given to consumers for complying with the waste management rules",
          "Bar code stickers attached to products to identify each type of plastic",
          "Plastic notes recovered from the waste recycling cycle",
          "Certificates of evidence of packaging waste recovered, reprocessed, or exported"
      ],
      "answer": "Certificates of evidence of packaging waste recovered, reprocessed, or exported"
  },
  {
      "question": "Waste-Free Ontario, 2016 enacts which of the following acts?",
      "options": [
          "The Resource Recovery and Circular Economy Act, 2016 & The Waste Diversion Transition Act, 2016",
          "The Resource Recovery and Circular Economy Act, 2016 & Canadian Environmental Protection Act, 2016",
          "The Waste Diversion Transition Act, 2016 & Canadian Environmental Protection Act, 2016",
          "The Resource Recovery and Circular Economy Act, 2016, The Waste Diversion Transition Act, 2016 & Canadian Environmental Protection Act, 2016"
      ],
      "answer": "The Resource Recovery and Circular Economy Act, 2016 & The Waste Diversion Transition Act, 2016"
  },
  {
      "question": "Which of the following is an interim goal set by Ontario to mark their progress and keep on track with their strategy to achieve a circular economy?",
      "options": [
          "25% diversion rate by 2020",
          "30% diversion rate by 2025",
          "50% diversion rate by 2040",
          "80% diversion rate by 2050"
      ],
      "answer": "80% diversion rate by 2050"
  },
  {
      "question": "With respect to the Waste-Free Ontario Act 2016, which of these act(s) establishes full producer responsibility by making them environmentally accountable and financially responsible for recovering resources and reducing waste associated with their products and packaging?",
      "options": [
          "Canadian Environmental Protection Act, 2016",
          "The Resource Recovery and Circular Economy Act, 2016",
          "The Waste Diversion Transition Act, 2016",
          "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "The Resource Recovery and Circular Economy Act, 2016"
  },
  {
      "question": "A circular economy is restorative and regenerative by design.",
      "options": [
          "True",
          "False"
      ],
      "answer": "True"
  },
  {
      "question": "Plastics are key enablers of a circular economy, directly facilitating the circularity of products and improving resource efficiency and sustainability along the value chain.",
      "options": [
          "True",
          "False"
      ],
      "answer": "True"
  },
  {
      "question": "Plastic circular economy helps in raising the negative environmental impacts of our production and consumption in the world.",
      "options": [
          "True",
          "False"
      ],
      "answer": "False"
  },
  {
      "question": "The goal to achieve a circular economy in Ontario is to attain zero waste Ontario and zero greenhouse gas emissions from the waste sector.",
      "options": [
          "True",
          "False"
      ],
      "answer": "True"
  },
  {
      "question": "To ensure landfills are well planned and managed to minimize their need to reduce greenhouse gas emissions is an action proposed towards Waste-Free Ontario.",
      "options": [
          "True",
          "False"
      ],
      "answer": "True"
  },
  ],
};
